{
    "subject": "resource/Clove_Furnace_Ruin",
    "predicate": "ontology/nearestCity",
    "object": "resource/Newburgh_(city),_New_York",
    "human_readable": "The nearest city to Clove Furnace Ruin is Newburgh (city), New York.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9833100438117981,
            "question": "Name the nearest city to Clove Furnace Ruin."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9773938655853271,
            "question": "Is Newburgh a nearby town or city to Clove Furnace Ruin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9664104580879211,
            "question": "Which city is closest to Clove Furnace Ruin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9541565179824829,
            "question": "What is the nearest city to Clove Furnace Ruin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8330331444740295,
            "question": "Where is Clove Furnace Ruin located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7901512384414673,
            "question": "In what location would you find Clove Furnace Ruin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7873410582542419,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Clove Furnace Ruin and Newburgh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6047947406768799,
            "question": "If you were visiting Clove Furnace Ruin, where would you go for amenities?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5978325605392456,
            "question": "Is Newburgh a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38392698764801025,
            "question": "What state is Newburgh in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The nearest city to Clove Furnace Ruin is Newburgh (city), New York.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2711_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Newburgh a city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2711_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were visiting Clove Furnace Ruin, where would you go for amenities?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2711_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Clove Furnace Ruin and Newburgh?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2711_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2711_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2711_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2711_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2711_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2711_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2711_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2711_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2711_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2711_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2711_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents mention Clove Furnace Ruin's location in Arden, NY and its proximity to the Thruway, they do not specify  Newburgh as the nearest city. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for the answer is that none of the documents mention Newburgh, NY as a city near Clove Furnace Ruin. In fact, according to document 7 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2711/re-ranker-msmarco/7.txt), the location is Arden, NY, and in document 47 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2711/re-ranker-msmarco/47.txt), a city called Cold Spring, NY is mentioned as related to the Clove Furnace Ruin."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents do not contain any information that suggests the nearest city to Clove Furnace Ruin is Newburgh, New York. The documents provide details about the location of the Clove Furnace and its historical context but do not mention Newburgh as being close to it."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}